Guide to the Felix S. Cohen Papers Addition
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Felix S. Cohen Papers Addition
1927-1960
1931-1953
WA MSS S-2602
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
25.91
(31 boxes)
The Felix S. Cohen Papers Addition documents aspects of Cohen's legal career as a civil servant, private attorney, and author, as well as his social, political, and professional activities. Included are files stemming from Cohen's work as a legislative draftsman and solicitor for the Department of the Interior, relating especially to Indian affairs and natural resources, and his work as a private attorney, relating to Indian affairs, immigration, and voting rights, including his manuscript notes for oral arguments in the cases of Trujillo vs. Garley and Harrison vs. Laveen; files relating to Cohen's various writing projects, comprising articles and reviews for law journals and published works, including Ethical Systems and Legal Ideals and The Legal Consicence; and extensive files stemming from his activities with the Socialist Party and the National Lawyers Guild and, to a lesser extent, with various other social, political, and legal organizations, including the League for Industrial Democracy and the Institute for Living Law. Also found are some professional and personal papers.
31 boxes (incl. 1 oversize box)
Cohen, Felix S., 1907-1953
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Gene Cohen Tweraser and Karen Cohen Holmes, 2007.
Conditions Governing Access
Box 31 (sound recordings): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Associated Materials
Associated material includes the Felix S. Cohen Papers, WA MSS S-1325.
Felix S. Cohen (1907-1953)
Felix Solomon Cohen was a lawyer with special interests in natural resources, in statehood and economic development for American territories, in Indian affairs, and in immigration and minority problems. He was a professor of jurisprudence, a civil servant, and an author of numerous articles on law, ethics, and philosophy, on Native Americans and minorities, and on human and natural resources. From 1933 through 1947 he served in the Solicitor's Office of the Department of Interior as an assistant solicitor, associate solicitor, and acting solicitor. He also served as chairman of the Office's Board of Appeals. Cohen drafted the Wheeler-Howard Act (later known as the Indian Reorganization Act) of 1934, and contributed to the department's handling of Indian and Eskimo aboriginal rights. In 1939 Cohen was named Chief of the Indian Law Survey, a joint project of the Lands Division of the Department of Justice and of the Department of Interior to compile all federal laws, treaties, etc., involving Native Americans. Cohen edited a summary of the 46-volume survey, which was published by the Interior Department as The Handbook of Federal Indian Law and remains a milestone in the evolution of Indian law. He received the Department's highest honor--the Distinguished Service Award--on retirement from government service in 1948.
Cohen re-entered private general law practice in January 1948, but continued to be interested in the legal affairs of Native Americans and immigrants, in human rights, and in natural resources. He eventually associated his Washington, D.C. office with the New York law firm of Riegelman, Strasser, Schwarz & Spiegelberg (which later became known in Washington as Fried, Frank, Harris, Shriver & Kampelman). Cohen handled several important pro bono Indian cases, particularly two lawsuits, Trujillo vs. Garley and Harrison vs. Laveen, which established Native Americans' rights to vote in the last two states that had denied the franchise to them--New Mexico and Arizona, as well as cases securing their right to receive Social Security benefits.
In 1946, Cohen had begun teaching legislative drafting and legal philosophy at Yale University's Law School, and jurisprudence at The City College of New York's Department of Philosophy. Cohen had also taught at the New School for School Research and the University of Newark Law School (later Rutgers Law School). In 1951 he published Readings in Jurisprudence and Legal Philosophy, the syllabus which he developed with his father, Morris R. Cohen, for both their jurisprudence courses (Morris Cohen at St. John's Law School and Felix Cohen at Rutgers and the New School for Social Research).
Felix S. Cohen was born in Manhattan, but grew up in Yonkers, New York. He attended The City College of New York, received an M.A. in philosophy from Harvard in 1927 and a Ph.D. from Harvard in 1929. In 1928 Cohen entered Columbia Law School, graduating in 1931. He married Lucy M. Kramer that year; they had two daughters. He died at his home in Washington, D.C., in October 1953.
This biographical note is drawn from the finding aid for the Felix S. Cohen Papers, WA MSS S-1325.
Scope and Contents
The Felix S. Cohen Papers Addition comprises the remainder of the collection that was donated in 1989 and 1991. The addition consists of material that was stored in the basement and other areas of the Cohen residence in Washington, D. C. and that came to light after the death of Lucy Kramer Cohen in 2007. The additional material spans the period from 1925 to 1960, with the bulk of the material dating from 1931 to 1953, and documents aspects of Cohen's legal career as a civil servant, private attorney, and author, as well as his social, political, and professional activities.
Included in the addition are files stemming from Cohen's work as a legislative draftsman and solicitor for the Department of the Interior, relating especially to Indian affairs and natural resources, and his work as a private attorney, relating to Indian affairs, immigration, and voting rights, including his manuscript notes for oral arguments in the cases of Trujillo vs. Garley and Harrison vs. Laveen; files relating to Cohen's various writing projects, comprising articles and reviews for law journals and published works, including Ethical Systems and Legal Ideals and The Legal Consicence; and extensive files stemming from his activities with the Socialist Party and the National Lawyers Guild and, to a lesser extent, with various other social, political, and legal organizations, including the League for Industrial Democracy and the Institute for Living Law. Also found are some professional and personal papers.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into five series: I. Legal Career, 1930-1955. II. Professional Papers, 1931-1960. III. Writing Projects, 1927-1960. IV. Organizational Affiliations, 1927-1954. V. Personal Papers, circa 1925-1960.
Ethical systems and legal ideals: an essay on the foundations of legal criticism; Handbook of Federal Indian Law; The legal conscience, selected papers; Indians of North America -- Government relations -- 1934-; Indians of North America -- Legal status, laws, etc.; Suffrage -- United States; Audiovisual materials; Sound recordings; Lawyers -- United States; Austen, Harry -- Trials, litigation, etc.; Cohen, Felix S., 1907-1953; Cohen, Lucy Kramer, 1907-2007; Garley, Eloy -- Trials, litigation, etc.; Harrison, Frank -- Trials, litigation, etc.; Laveen, Roger G. -- Trials, litigation, etc.; Trujillo, Miguel N. -- Trials, litigation, etc.; United States. Department of the Interior; United States. Office of Indian Affairs; Institute of Living Law; League for Industrial Democracy; National Lawyers Guild; Socialist Party (U.S.)
- Legal Career, 1930-1955; Series I; 8; (8 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  The Legal Career series consists of files stemming from Cohen's work with the Solicitor's Office of the Department of Interior from 1933 to 1947 and with his private practice from 1948 to 1953.
  Arrangement
  This Legal Career series is arranged into four subseries: Indian Affairs, Indian Law Survey, Solicitor's Office Records, and Private Practice Office Records.
  - Indian Affairs, 1930-1942
    This subseries consists of Department of Interior files largely documenting the drafting and implementation of the Indian Reorganization Act of 1934 (IRA, known originally as the Wheeler-Howard Act) and routine legal work concerning the department's Indian policies. The files consist of internal memoranda, correspondence, drafts of reports and legal opinions, printed bills and drafts, and printed material by government agencies and private institutions.
    Files are arranged in rough chronological order.
    - Bills and Notes on Incorporation, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Anthropolgy Questionnaire, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Anthropology, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary drafts of Indian Self-Government Bill, circa 1934 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
    - Wheeler-Howard Bill File, Drafts and correspondence, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    - Wheeler-Howard Indian Bill, Correspondence, charter recommendations, atlas, publicity, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Departmental Report, Drafts and Analysis, circa 1934 (Box 1, Folder 9-11)
    - Indian Tribal Powers, circa 1934 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Drafts and revisions, circa 1934 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - General Notes on Proposed Legislation - Siegel, Shepard, Marshall, circa 1934 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Speeches, etc - Drafts, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Department Report on Wheeler-Howard Indian Rights Bill, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Hearings and testimony on Wheeler-Howard Act, circa 1934 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Tribal hearings on Wheeler-Howard Bill, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Official Indian Vote on Wheeler-Howard Bill, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Wheeler-Howard Bill, Publicity, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Congressional Bills on Indian Self-Government, Drafts, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 21-22)
    - "Solicitor's Opinion: Powers of Indian Tribes" (1934), circa 1934 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Indian Service and Self-Government, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Indian Constitutions, circa 1934 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Tribal Constitutions, 1934-1936 (Box 2, Folder 26-29)
    - Indian Legislation, 74th Congress, 1935 January 3 - June 15 (Box 2, Folder 30-31)
    - Repeal of Obsolete Laws, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Legal Matters, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Law and Order Regulations, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Indian Rights, circa 1935 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Court of Indian Affairs, circa 1935 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Wheeler-Howard Act
      - General, circa 1935 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Sec. 1-2 [empty folder], circa 1935 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Sec. 3, circa 1935 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Sec. 4-5, circa 1935 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Sec. 6-15, circa 1935 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Sec. 16, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Sec. 17, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Sec. 18-19, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Memoranda - Explanatory, circa 1935 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Memoranda - Critical, circa 1935 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Memo on Law and Order, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Winter Counts, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 48-49)
    - Land Assignment Forms, 1936-1937, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Office of Indian Affairs, Radio Programs, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Alaska Bill, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Indian Land Consolidation Program, 1937-1942 (Box 3, Folder 53-55)
    - Memorandum for Mr. Woehlke, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - New York Indians, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - "Indians at Work", 1939 February (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Legislative History of Wheeler-Howard Act [divider] (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Hearings, Reports and Speeches in Congress, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Bills - Legislative History, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Interpretation of Wheeler-Howard Act [divider] (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - General Interpretation, 1934-1936 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Black Hills Conference, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 64-65)
    - Government Publications, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - The Indian's Story, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Wheeler-Howard Bill, LK, circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Indian Affairs, Trips, etc., circa 1940 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Indian Claims Commission Act, Original Drafts, circa 1940 (Box 4, Folder 70-106)
    - "Legislative Material on the Indian Claims Commission Act of 1946", circa 1946 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Indian Law Survey, 1939-1940
    This subseries consists of files stemming from a joint project of the Department of Interior and Department of Justice, on which Cohen served as chief, to create a file of federal legislation and treaties concerning Native Americans. The project resulted in an internal publication entitled "Statutory Compilation of the Indian Law Survey: A Compendium of Federal Laws and Treaties Relating to Indians" and The Handbook of Federal Indian Law. The files consist primarily of memoranda, research material, and drafts.
    Files are arranged in no particular order.
    Related Archival Materials note
    More extensive documentation relating to the Indian Law Survey project can be found in the Felix S. Cohen Papers, WA MSS S-1325.
    - Department of Justice Memoranda - Application Memos, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Daybook 1, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 109-110)
    - "Chap. 3 Indian Treaties, Chap. 9 Individual Rights in Tribal Prop., Chap. 10 The Rights of the Indian in his Personality", 1940 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - "Chapters 3-9-10, 12-18, 25-27", 1939 (Box 4, Folder 112-114)
    - Lists of Court Cases Regarding Indian Affairs, undated (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Regulations of Indian Service, undated (Box 4, Folder 116-117)
    - "Indian Constitutions, Volume I", undated (Box 4, Folder 118-121)
    - Handbook of Federal Indian Law, Preliminary drafts, Chapters 1 and 3, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 122-123)
  - Solicitor's Office Records, 1934-1947
    This subseries consists of files relating to Cohen's work with the Solicitor's Office on issues pertaining to natural resources, including government control of coal mines during the Second World War and the use of helium as an enery source. The files consist of memoranda, correspondence, drafts of reports and legal opinions, and printed material. Also found are various government publications.
    Files within this subseries are arranged into three groupings: Coal Files, Helium Files, and Printed Material. Files within each grouping are arranged in rough chronological order.
    - Coal Files
      - Coal, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 124)
      - Coal, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 125-126)
      - Bituminous Coal Miscellaneous, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 127)
      - Guffey Coal Act, 1935-1937 (Box 5, Folder 128-132)
      - Consumers' Counsel, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 133)
      - Consumers' Counsel Division, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 134-137)
      - Coal, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 138)
      - Midland Case, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 139)
      - Coal Mines Take-Over, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 140)
      - Control of Coal Mines, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 141)
      - Coal Operations, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 142)
      - Regulations for the Operations of Coal Mines Under Government Control, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 143-144)
      - Mine Safety Legislation, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 145)
      - Moot Court Cases, undated (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - Helium Files
      - Helium, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 147-148)
      - Helium, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 149)
      - Publicity, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 150)
      - Synopsis, Solicitor's Opinion, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 151)
      - Memos and Letters, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 152-154)
      - Pending Matters, 1938-1940 (Box 6, Folder 155-156)
      - Helium Reference Documents, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 157)
      - Memoranda, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 158)
      - Helium, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 159)
      - Laws and Regulations, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 160)
      - Testimony and Hearings, undated (Box 6, Folder 161-163)
    - Printed Material
      - Self-Help Cooperatives - FERA, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 164)
      - Alaskan Development, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 165)
      - War Relocation Authority, circa 1940 (Box 6, Folder 166)
  - Private Practice Office Records, 1949-1955
    This subseries consists of files stemming from Cohen's private legal practice and relating to Indian affairs, immigration, and voting rights. Of particular note are Cohen's manuscript notes for his oral argument, of which no printed record exists, in the case of Trujillo vs. Garley, an Indian voting rights case in New Mexico.
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Chronological Files, 1949 January - June (Box 6, Folder 167-172)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Chronological Files, 1949 July - 1951 October (Box 7, Folder 173-199)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Chronological Files, 1951 November - 1953 October (Box 8, Folder 200-211)
    - Trujillo vs. Garley and Harrison vs. Laveen (New Mexico and Arizona voting rights) with notes, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 212)
    - Trujillo vs. Garley, New Mexico's Voting Case - Manuscript Notes for Argument, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 213)
    - Materials regarding "Blackfeet", 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 214)
    - Blackfoot Brief on Housing, Photographs, 1950 March (Box 8, Folder 215)
    - Telegram, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 216)
    - "Summary Analysis of Proposed Omnibus Immigration Bill", 1951 March 21 (Box 8, Folder 217)
    - Briefs to Supreme Court of New York County, circa 1952 (Box 8, Folder 218)
    - Immigration, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 219)
    - Joint Efforts - Land Value Memorial (AL), 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 220)
    - Joint Efforts General - Tabulations on Cases, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 221)
    - Non-Joint Efforts - Office Memos, Briefs, etc., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 222)
    - Joint Efforts - Office Memos, Briefs, etc., 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 223-225)
- Professional Papers, 1931-1960; Series II; 1.04; (3 boxes)
  This series consists of scattered papers and office files that relate broadly to Cohen's professional activities as a lawyer. Material found here overlaps with that found amongst the Legal Career files.
  Material is arranged in rough chronological order. Miscellaneous and unsorted material are arranged at the end.
  - Bar Admission, circa 1932 (Box 9, Folder 226)
  - Early Career, Memoranda on Cases, 1931-1933 (Box 9, Folder 227-230)
  - Law Practice, Memos, etc., 1934-1937 (Box 9, Folder 231)
  - Miscellaneous (from Felix S. Cohen's desk), 1940s (Box 9, Folder 232)
  - "Book I. Legal Institutions", Typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 233)
  - Expenses, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 234-237)
  - French Report on U. S. Indians, undated (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - Paper for 13th Conference on Science, Philosophy, and Religion, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 239)
  - Papers from Conference on Moral Standards, 1953 September (Box 10, Folder 240)
  - Alaska's Nuremberg Laws, circa 1954 (Box 10, Folder 241)
  - Alaska Photographs, undated (Box 10, Folder 242)
  - Printed Material on American Indians, 1953, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 243)
  - Blank Stationary, undated (Box 10, Folder 244)
  - "Material to be read by FSC", 1951-1953 (Box 10, Folder 245-247)
  - Awards and Honors, 1946-1960 (Box 10, Folder 248)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940s-1950s (Box 10, Folder 249-250)
  - Other Papers, undated (Box 11, Folder 251-254)
- Writing Projects, 1927-1960; Series III; 5.2; (6 boxes)
  The Writing Projects series consists of notes, background material, manuscripts and drafts, and correspondence relating to articles and book reviews by Cohen that appeared in various law journals and relating to his book, Ethical Systems and Legal Ideals, which was originally published in 1933; drafts for a work on Indian land values; notes and drafts for lectures on various topics; and correspondence and source material for the posthumous compilation of Cohen's writings entitled The Legal Conscience, edited by Lucy Kramer Cohen, which was published in 1960. Also found are scattered writings by others, and offprints and publications of writings by and about Cohen.
  The Writing Projects series is arranged into seven subseries: Articles and Reviews, Ethical Systems and Legal Ideals, Indian Land Values, Lectures, The Legal Conscience, Writings by Others, and Printed Material.
  - Articles and Reviews
    Files are largely arranged in rough chronological order. Miscellaneous and undated material are arranged at the end.
    - Notes, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 255)
    - More Notes on Freedom, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 256)
    - "What is a Question", 1929-1930 (Box 12, Folder 257)
    - Legal Book Reviews, 1931-1941 (Box 12, Folder 258-260)
    - "The Subject Matter of Ethical Studies", 1931-1932 (Box 13, Folder 261-262)
    - "Ethical Basis of Legal Criticisim", Correspondence, 1931-1932 (Box 13, Folder 263)
    - Review of Boudin, "Government by Judiciary" - notes, manuscript, circa 1932 (Box 13, Folder 264)
    - "Summary Judgements", Correspondence, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 265)
    - Manchuria, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 266)
    - The Student Outlook, 1932-1933 (Box 13, Folder 267-268)
    - "The Blessing of Unemployment", 1933 (Box 13, Folder 269-270)
    - Perishable Food Industries, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 271-273)
    - Notes on Perishable Food Industries, circa 1933 (Box 13, Folder 274)
    - Bentham Review, Yale Law Journal, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 275)
    - Article on Benjamin Cardoza, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 276)
    - "Modern Ethics and the Law", 1934 (Box 13, Folder 277)
    - "Transcendental Nonsense and the Functional Approach", 1935-1937 (Box 13, Folder 278-282)
    - "Socialism and the Myth of Legality", 1935-1936 (Box 13, Folder 283-288)
    - "Socialization of Morality", 1935-1939 (Box 14, Folder 289-291)
    - Review of Ehrlich, "Fundamental Principles of the Sociology of Law", 1936 (Box 14, Folder 292)
    - "Government and the Social Contract", 1936 (Box 14, Folder 293)
    - Material on Workmen's Compensation, 1936-1937 (Box 14, Folder 294)
    - Columbia Law Review - Notes, etc., circa 1937 (Box 14, Folder 295)
    - "The Relativity of Philosophical Systems and the Method of Systematic Relativism", 1937-1939 (Box 14, Folder 296-299)
    - "The Supreme Court and Religious Liberty", 1937 (Box 14, Folder 300)
    - "The Problems of Functional Jurisprudence", 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 301)
    - "What City College Will Contribute to the Development of Law", 1938 (Box 14, Folder 302)
    - "Democracy and the War", 1942 (Box 14, Folder 303-305)
    - Readings in Jurisprudence and Legal Philosophy, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 306-310)
    - Encyclopedia articles on casuistry and Lorimer, James, undated (Box 14, Folder 311)
    - Law Review Invitations, etc., 1935-1939 (Box 14, Folder 312)
    - Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 14, Folder 313)
    - "Dialogue on Private Property", undated (Box 14, Folder 314)
    - City College, undated (Box 14, Folder 315)
    - Miscellaneous reviews, etc. - Offprints, undated (Box 14, Folder 316)
    - "Notes on Fictions" and other notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 317)
    - Unclaimed contributions to poetry readings, undated (Box 14, Folder 318)
    - Bibliography and offprints, undated (Box 14, Folder 319)
    - Notecards, undated (Box 14, Folder 320)
  - Ethical Systems and Legal Ideals (1933)
    - Manuscripts, circa 1933 (Box 14, Folder 321)
    - Manuscripts, circa 1933 (Box 15, Folder 322-329)
    - Notes and Miscellaneous Papers, circa 1933 (Box 15, Folder 330)
    - Correspondence with publishers, 1933-1938 (Box 15, Folder 331)
    - Correspondence and reviews, 1933-1934 (Box 15, Folder 332)
    - Book Review Digest, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 333)
  - Indian Land Values, undated
    - Indian Land Values, undated (Box 15, Folder 334-336)
  - Lectures
    - "Lectures" [divider], undated (Box 15, Folder 337)
    - Regulation of Hours and Wages, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 338)
    - Contemporary Legal Thought in America, undated (Box 15, Folder 339-340)
    - American Federation of Government Employees, 1936-1937 (Box 16, Folder 341-343)
    - Miscellaneous, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 344)
    - League for Industrial Democracy, circa 1936 (Box 16, Folder 345)